FARRELL ADRA KHALFANI

BACKEND ENGINEER

South Tangerang, Indonesia

+628174897999

farrell.khalfani47@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

Recent college graduate with a Bachelor of Computer Science seeking to join as an entry-level backend engineer. Aiming to leverage acquired 1+ year experience to successfully fill the backend engineer role at your company. Competencies in diverse programming languages, such as PHP, Python, and Golang. Eager to learn new things and be a better software engineer.

EDUCATION -

2016 - 2020

Bachelor's Degree of Computer Science (S1),

Bina Nusantara University, Tangerang, Banten

KEY SKILLS —

Proficient:

- PHP, Laravel / Lumen
- MySQL
- Git
- HTML/CSS/JS

Familiar:

- Python
- Golang
- Node.js
- AngularJS

LANGUAGES —

- Indonesia (Native)
- English (Proficient)

EXPERIENCE

March 2020 – April 2020

Backend Engineer • Ralali.com B2B Marketplace

 Developed API endpoints to serve Ralali's logistic management platforms that tracks the progress of integrated 3rd party delivery services.

March 2019 – March 2020

Intern Backend Engineer • Ralali.com B2B Marketplace

- Improved the security of Ralali Giftcard's promo code redeeming process thus reducing the percentage of fraud cases.
- Revamped Ralali's Seller Panel by developing API endpoints that generates sales report and strategic data to help sellers optimize their profit.
- Developed a CMS feature flag (feature toggle) for Ralali's mobile app.
- Developed a CMS feature for the version management of Ralali's mobile app.

Technology Stacks: PHP, Laravel, Lumen; MySQL, AngularJS